ellusionist.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy and Security | Ellusionist online Magic Store

This website uses cookies to ensure proper functionality of the shopping cart and checkout progress. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to the use of cookies.   
You may change your preference at any time by clicking accept or decline as shown below. 

## We Respect your privacy

We value your privacy, and promise never to sell or rent your email address or personal information for your lifetime.

Please note, our privacy policy has been updated as of May 23/2018. Please read everything. Significant changes have been made concerning the collection of Personal Identifying Information and how it is used exclusively for use by Ellusionist and it's partners.

The Ellusionist Store uses industry-standard SSL (256-bit Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information during transmission over the Internet. Our privacy policy insures that your information is fully secure and protected. 

Thank you for your interest in ellusionist.com (“ellusionist®”) and our website located at [www.ellusionist.com](https://www.ellusionist.com/).  We are pleased to provide this privacy policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use personally identifiable information about visitors to our website.  By using this website, you consent to the following terms.

###  **Children's Online Privacy Policy**

ellusionist® has adopted special procedures applicable to personal information from children under the age of 13 in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. [Click to read the Children's Privacy Policy](https://www.ellusionist.com/privacy-security#cps). Any conflicting portions of our general Privacy Policy are superceded by this Policy. 

### **What personal information does Ellusionist collect?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve Ellusionist's shopping and community experience. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give while registering and account or placing an order.  You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our site.

**Mobile** : When you download or use apps created by Ellusionist, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to validate the mobile app purchases, and/or provide updates and notifications. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services.

**E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail if your computer supports such capabilities. We use this information to gather information that allows us to improve our communications to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your preferences in your account (if you have one) or click the 'unsubscribe' link found at the bottom of all non-order related emails .

### **What About Cookies?**

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide valuable features which can enhance the use of our site, most importantly pertaining to the storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any product or service that require you to Log In.

### **Do We Share the Information We Receive?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below.

**Third-Party Service Providers** : We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Protection of Ellusionist and Others** : We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Ellusionist, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

### **How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

### **Which Information Can I Access?**

We give you access to a broad range of information about your account and in certain cases, updating that information. 

### **What Choices Do I Have?**

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of features that are important to the use of our site.

When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your newsletter settings and unsubscribe from mailing lists. This will not prevent order confirmation/shipping or other order/product related information that we may need to send to you as a part of our ensuring you have access to complete and up to date information. (If you do not want to receive emails from us, it is your responsibility to review our conditions of use and privacy policy for changes.)

If you do not want us to use personal information that we gather to allow third parties to personalize advertisements we display to you, please adjust your decline the cookie notice shown to you when you visit our site.

The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Amazon.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Amazon.com products and services that require you to Sign in.

### **Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Ellusionist, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at Ellusionist.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

### Examples of Information Collected

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us) or Your Profile ; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile Wish Lists  provide and rate Reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers) content of reviews and e-mails to us.

**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features like Top Sellers ; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for. We may also use browser data such as cookies, or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.

**Mobile**

Most mobile devices provide users with the ability to disable location services. Most likely, these controls are located in the device's settings menu. For information about specific devices, click here. If you have questions about how to disable your device's location services, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.

**Information from Other Sources**

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features; information we use to help prevent and detect fraud.

**Information You Can Access**

Examples of information you can access easily include up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, communications preferences, address book, e-mail notification settings (including newsletters); wishlists and cart).

**Your Right to your information**

You have a right to access your information, and limit access to your information. Should you decide that you don't want any of your personal identifying information (PII) being used tracking and third party information will be restricted and not sent to those services, but cookies used only at Ellusionist will still be used, for shopping cart purposes and tying your account to your browser session. These cookies are required for us to allow you to check out. Additionally, you may submit a request to support@ellusionist.com to have your information removed from third party services, however you will need to verify your identity via legal identification in order for us to verify the identity of the account and the person making the request. Further, you may request deletion of your account from Ellusionist. While we cannot delete orders, we can anonymize order data and delete accounts, however this means that you will no longer be able to log in to access downloads you have purchased in the past. If a purchase has been made, we are legally required to maintain the integrity of that information and are required to keep a copy of the transaction for legal purposes. Access to this information is tracked and kept secure at all times. Ellusionist will make every effort to remove all PII from all services that we use when a request has been made and verified. 

**Disclosure**

ellusionist® uses certain third party vendors (e.g., data storage and processing facilities and order processing services) to assist ellusionist® in providing our products and services.  ellusionist® may transfer your personally identifiable information to such vendors who have entered into an arrangement to with ellusionist® that protects the confidentiality of your information and permits the vendor to use it only as reasonably necessary to fulfill its contract with ellusionist®.  ellusionist® may also disclose your personally identifiable information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority.  Finally, ellusionist® may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of ellusionist®’s assets or stock in ellusionist®’s line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization. 

**Links**

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services.  If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not ellusionist®’s, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

**Security**

ellusionist® employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service, reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Updating Your Information**

You may update your information by sending an email to [support@ellusionist.com](mailto:support@ellusionist.com) or calling **one of the phone numbers listed below**.

**Policy Changes**

ellusionist® reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on its website located at [www.ellusionist.com](https://www.ellusionist.com/).  We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.  Your continued use of this web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

**Questions?**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at [support@ellusionist.com](mailto:support@ellusionist.com) or by phone at one of the numbers listed below.

* * *

**Children's Online Privacy Policy**

ellusionist® has adopted special procedures applicable to personal information from children under the age of 13 in compliance with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998](https://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm). Any conflicting portions of our general Privacy Policy are superceded by this Policy. 

**Contact Information**

You may contact ellusionist at:  
P. O. Box 11623  
San Rafael, CA  
94912

US & Canada Telephone (Toll Free): 1-866-244-2426   
International Telephone: 1-415-459-4945

**What personal information do we collect from children?**

After ellusionist® receives, via mail or fax, a consent form signed by a parent or guardian, we may collect contact information (name and/or e-mail address _),_ and if products are purchased, we may collect a credit card number and expiration date. A visit to the Site will not provide us with information by which we could personally identify a child. Uses of personal information and disclosure practices are described further in our general privacy policy and on the parental consent form. 

**How do we protect information about children?**

Registration information submitted by a child's parent cannot be modified except through submission of a modified parental consent form or other written request. All such information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons and contractors who have special access rights to such systems. All contractors have agreed to keep this information confidential.

**How can parents review their child's personal information and prevent its use or disclosure?**

A parent or guardian who permits personal information to be collected about their child may also submit a signed written request to review or modify the information about their child. We will delete personal information about a child upon receipt of a written request from the parent or guardian who initially submitted such information. In the event of such a request, we will retain only information necessary for record keeping and customer service for past transactions.
